<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SMART AIR</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="enter_email_or_username">Enter Email or Username</string>
    <string name="enter_password">Enter Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="click_to_register">Click to register</string>
    <string name="parentf1">parentf1</string>
    <string name="add_child">Add child</string>
    <string name="manage_child">View Children</string>
    <string name="add_child_prompt">Create an account for your child</string>
    <string name="manage_child_prompt">Access your children\'s accounts</string>
    <string name="child_signup_username">Enter Username</string>
    <string name="domain">\@smartairchildaccount.com</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="enter_dob">Enter Birth Date (optional)</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter Name (optional)</string>
    <string name="add_child_header">Creating an Account for your Child</string>
    <string name="select_child">Select child</string>
    <string name="change_child_settings">Enter new value</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="click_to_edit">Click on an item to edit its value!</string>
    <string name="view_child_profile">View as child</string>
    <string name="generate_code">Generate code</string>
    <string name="regenerate_code">Regenerate code</string>
    <string name="revoke_code">Revoke code</string>
    <string name="share">Share with provider</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to SMARTAIR!</string>
    <string name="swipe">You will now see an explanation of the app, swipe right on each page to continue!</string>
    <string name="not_child_purpose">SMART AIR is a child-friendly platform to help children (ages 6–16) understand asthma, practice good inhaler technique, log symptoms/medicine use, and share parent-approved information with healthcare providers via a concise, exportable report.</string>
    <string name="child_purpose">SMART AIR is an app to help children like you learn about asthma, practice using inhalers properly, and write down whenever you use medicine or feel any symptoms so that your parents and doctors can see it!</string>
    <string name="as_a_parent">As a parent, you can add and manage your children\'s accounts, view all of their medicine logs, symptoms, daily check ins, and more, share data that you choose with their providers, and receive alerts about any worrying situations related to your children.</string>
    <string name="our_purpose">Our Purpose:</string>
    <string name="what_you_see">What you see:</string>
    <string name="rescue_vs_controller">Rescue vs Controller Medicine:</string>
    <string name="rescue_controller_definition">A rescue inhaler provides quick-relief medicine for sudden symptoms. Controller medicine is daily prevention medicine that reduces airway swelling.</string>
    <string name="as_a_provider">As a provider, you can enter invite codes shared by parents to view reports of their children\'s data, containing only information that they have shared. Parents can revoke this access at any time. A code is valid for 7 days, but once you enter a code, you will have access to the corresposnding report until parents revoke it. You can only read the data, you can\'t edit any of it.</string>
    <string name="as_a_child">As a child, you will see helpful videos that help you take your medicine properly. You will be able to enter your feelings, symptoms, and how well you can breathe every morning and every time you take medicine. If you are ever having trouble breathing, you will always be able to click a simple button, that will help you through your situation.</string>
    <string name="parent_owns_child">Your parent owns your account. They choose your username, password, and settings, and they decide what to do with your data. If you don\'t understand something, make sure to ask your parents!</string>
    <string name="next">Continue to dashboard</string>
    <string name="shared_data">Things that a parent can choose to share with you: rescue logs, controller adherence summary, symptoms, triggers, peak-flow (PEF), triage incidents, and summary charts (visuals representing the other data).</string>
    <string name="invite_title">Provider Sharing Controls:</string>
    <string name="sharing_controls">You will be able to generate an invite code, and your provider will have 7 days to enter this code to gain access to the information that you toggle on. You can revoke provider access or regenerate this code at any time. By default, all data will be kept private, so that only you and your child will be able to view it.</string>
    <string name="managing_title">Managing Children Accounts:</string>
    <string name="child_controls">You can create an account for your child with a username and password at any time. You can also configure many settings for them, such as their name, age, personal best peak-flow (PB), thresholds to earn badges, and action plans for when your child is in the green, orange, or red zone (% peak-flow (PEF) of PB).</string>
</resources>